Henry B. Ward Papers 1859-1942 1888-1933 Mss.Ms.Coll.41
American Philosophical Society
- Henry B. Ward Papers, 1859-1942; 1.75 lin. feet
  - Morgan, W. P., 1917 (Box 2)
  - Morton, J. Sterling, 1897 (Box 2)
  - Mrazek, Al., 1914 (Box 2)
  - Muir, John, 1904 (Box 2)
  - Muller, Reiner, 1922 (Box 2)
  - Mundt, Karl, 1939 (Box 2)
  - Munson, W. H., 1899 (Box 2)
  - Murray Alfred, 1919 (Box 2)
  - Nabours, R. K., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Nachtrieb, Henry F., 1899-1915 (Box 3)
  - Needham, James, 1907 (Box 3)
  - Neidlinger, W. H., 1918 (Box 3)
  - Nelson, E. W., 1920 (Box 3)
  - Neumann, L. G., 1897, 1914 (Box 3)
  - Newell?, F. H., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Newman, H. H., 1920 (Box 3)
  - Nice, L. B., 1921 (Box 3)
  - Nicoll, A. S.?, 1930 (Box 3)
  - Noble, Robert E., 1920, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Naller, W., 1923 (Box 3)
  - Norman, W. W., 1894 (Box 3)
  - Norris, H. W., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Nory, F. G., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Noyes, W. E., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Nuttall, G. H. F., 1905-1927 (Box 3)
  - Nutting, Charles Cleveland, 1912 (Box 3)
  - Olive, Edgar W., 1912 (Box 3)
  - O'Malley, Henry, 1918-1921 (Box 3)
  - Ondemans, A. C., 1893, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Oahuer, T., 1916 (Box 3)
  - Ortmann, A. E., 1915 (Box 3)
  - Osborn, Henry Fairfield, 1903 (Box 3)
  - Osborn, Henry L., 1917, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Osborn, Herbert, 1902, 1915 (Box 3)
  - Osburn, Raymond C., 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Ott, H. N., 1909 (Box 3)
  - Ozaki, Yoshimasa, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Paddock, George A., 1941 (Box 3)
  - Paine, Baynard H., 1897 (Box 3)
  - Papov, A., 1932 (Box 3)
  - Parker, George Howard, 1894-1920 (Box 3)
  - Parker, Horatio N., 1900? (Box 3)
  - Parker, Gilbert, 1915 (Box 3)
  - Patching, Fred, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Patten, Bradley M., 1920-1921 (Box 3)
  - Patten, William, 1901 (Box 3)
  - Patterson, J. T., 1918 (Box 3)
  - Pavlovsky, E. N., 1931? (Box 3)
  - Payne, F., 1915 (Box 3)
  - Pearce, Richard Mills, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Pearl, Raymond, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Pearse, A. S., 1912, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Peckham, George Williams, 1904 (Box 3)
  - Peebles, Florence, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Pegram, George B., 1933 (Box 3)
  - Pentelow, F. T. K., 1926 (Box 3)
  - Perkins, H. F., 1914 (Box 3)
  - Perronisto, E., 1914-1928 (Box 3)
  - Perry, Arthur E., 1909 (Box 3)
  - Perry, Bliss, 1936 (Box 3)
  - Peter, Alfred M., 1921 (Box 3)
  - Pflaum, Magnus, 1896 (Box 3)
  - Phelps, William Lyon, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Phillips, John C., 1929 (Box 3)
  - Pierce, W. Dwight, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Pintner, Thomas, 1892-1927 (Box 3)
  - Plotz, Harry, 1931 (Box 3)
  - Poche, F., 1924 (Box 3)
  - Porsild, Morten, 1919-1923 (Box 3)
  - Porter, Carlos, 1914, 1915 (Box 3)
  - Portmann, Adolph, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Pats, Mariano, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Potts, Edward, 1907 (Box 3)
  - Potts, F. A., n.d. (Box 3)
  - Pound, Roscoe, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Poynter, C. W. M., 1920 (Box 3)
  - Pratt, Henry S., 1894-l918 (Box 3)
  - Pratt, George D., 1918, 1932 (Box 3)
  - Pruvot, G., 1900 (Box 3)
  - Pusey, William Allen, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Ramaley, Francis, 1902 (Box 3)
  - Ransom, B. H., 1909-1924 (Box 3)
  - Railliet, A., 1914-1916 (Box 3)
  - Rappleye Willard C., 1918, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Rate, Stefan von, 1914, l915 (Box 3)
  - Raud, Herbert W., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Redfield, C. L., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Reed, J. A., 1920 (Box 3)
  - Reese, A. M., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Regan, Nate, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Reigard, Jacob, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Rhodes, Robert C., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Rice, Edward L., 1909 (Box 3)
  - Richards, A., 1918-1921 (Box 3)
  - Richards, J., 1899-1905 (Box 3)
  - Ridgway, Robert, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Riel, V., 1924 (Box 3)
  - Riley, C. F. Curtis, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Riley, William A., 1918, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Robertson, A. Willis, 1935 (Box 3)
  - Robertson, W. R. B., 1918 (Box 3)
  - Robinson, B. L., 1895? (Box 3)
  - Ritter, William Emerson, 1899-1919 (Box 3)
  - Robinson, Arthur R., 1931 (Box 3)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore Jr., 1935 (Box 3)
  - Root, Francis M., 1921 (Box 3)
  - Rosa, Daniel, 1892-1899 (Box 3)
  - Rose, 1894 (Box 3)
  - Ross, C. Ben, 1931 (Box 3)
  - Ross, J. C., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Rosseir?, L. B., 1909? (Box 3)
  - Roule, Louis, 1903? (Box 3)
  - Rousseau, E., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Rousselet, Charles F., 1904, 1906 (Box 3)
  - Ruckmich, Christian A., 1919, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Russell, J. R., 1919 (Box 3)
  - St. John, Larry, 1920-1921 (Box 3)
  - Sambon, Louis W., 1922-1923 (Box 3)
  - Schaefer, Edwin M., 1941 (Box 3)
  - Schaeffer, A., 1919-1920 (Box 3)
  - Schaudin, Fritz Richard, 1903; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Schauinsland, H., 1913 (Box 3)
  - Schneider, Edward C., 1917 (Box 3)
  - Schuetz, Leonard W., 1941 (Box 3)
  - Schweinitz, George E. de, 1931 (Box 3)
  - Scott, John W., 1914 (Box 3)
  - Scott, Will, 1921-1?23 (Box 3)
  - Sergent, Edmond, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Seton, Ernest T., 1902-1924 (Box 3)
  - Seurat, [L.]?, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Sewell, Henry, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Sewell, R. B. Seymour, 1920-1923 (Box 3)
  - Sharpe, R. W., 1911-1921 (Box 3)
  - Shedd, H. G., 1909 (Box 3)
  - Sherman, Stuart, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Shields, R. T., 1916 (Box 3)
  - Shipley, Arther, 1897-1926 (Box 3)
  - Shull, A. Franklin, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Shull, Charles A., 1921 (Box 3)
  - Sigerfoos, Charles P., 1920 (Box 3)
  - Silvester, F., 1906 (Box 3)
  - Simroth, H., 1895 (Box 3)
  - Sinitsin, D., 1930 (Box 3)
  - Skorikow, A., 1903 (Box 3)
  - Skrjabin, K., 1922 (Box 3)
  - Slansky, Jan E., n.d. (Box 3)
  - Slossick, W., 1894, 1904 (Box 3)
  - Slosson, Edwin E., 1918 (Box 3)
  - Snow?, Julia W., 1914 (Box 3)
  - Smith, Alexander (Box 3)
  - Smith, Bertram G., 1920 (Box 3)
  - Smith, George Williamson, 1892 (Box 3)
  - Smith, Harlan, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Smith, H. M., 1920-1921 (Box 3)
  - Southwell, T., 1914-1927 (Box 3)
  - Spengel, J. W., 1897-1905 (Box 3)
  - Stauffer, Th., 1894 (Box 3)
  - Stearns, Henry V., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Steck, Theodorel, 1897 (Box 3)
  - Stedman, Thomas L., 1915 (Box 3)
  - Steiner, G., 1920 (Box 3)
    German
  - Steiner, G., 1922 (Box 3)
    American
  - Stephans, G. W. W., 1905, 1930 (Box 3)
  - Stephens, T. C., 1920 (Box 3)
  - Stephenson, J., 1930 (Box 3)
  - Stever, Adolph, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Stewart, Charles L., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Stiles, C. W., 1920 (Box 3)
  - Stokes, A. C., 1909 (Box 3)
  - Stonie, G. H., 1910 (Box 3)
  - Strasburger, [S.]?, 1894 (Box 3)
  - Strassen, Otto zur, 1898?-1930 (Box 3)
  - Strohl, J., 1932 (Box 3)
  - Strom, K. Munster, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Stromsten, Frank A., 1920 (Box 3)
  - Strong, R. M., 1918, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Strong, Richard P., 1928 (Box 3)
  - Sumner, Jessie, 1941 (Box 3)
  - Sun, C. H., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Sun, F. T., 1918 (Box 3)
  - Sweet, Georgina, 1914-1920 (Box 3)
  - Swingle, Leroy D., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Swingle, W. W., 1921 (Box 3)
  - Sykes, George F., 1920 (Box 3)
  - Tafall, B. F. Osorio, 1941-1942 (Box 3)
  - Tanabe, B., 1923 (Box 3)
  - Taquet, Maurice, 1895 (Box 3)
  - Terry, R. J., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Thomas, A. O., 1909 (Box 3)
  - Thompson, C. B., 1920-1921 (Box 3)
  - Thompson, G. H., 1916-1920 (Box 3)
  - Thompson, J. A., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Thompson, James, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Thompson, W. T., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Thomson, John Arthur, 1930 (Box 3)
  - Thorne, Charles H., 1920-1921 (Box 3)
  - Thuringer, Joseph M., 1921 (Box 3)
  - Tiling, Johannes von, 1903 (Box 3)
  - Torrey, Harry Beal, 1921-1926 (Box 3)
  - Tower, W. L., 1901 (Box 3)
  - Townsend, Charles H., 1920 (Box 3)
  - Transeau, E. N., 1913 (Box 3)
  - Trelease, William, 1916-1918 (Box 3)
  - Tsunema?, Lisube?, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Tubangui, M. A., 1922-1923 (Box 3)
  - Tucker, Francis F., 1918-1919 (Box 3)
  - Tyler, A. A., 1909-1920 (Box 3)
  - Tyzzer, E. E., 1918 (Box 3)
  - Uhlworm, D., 1894-1895 (Box 3)
  - University of London Animal Welfare Society, 1932, 1933 (Box 3)
  - University of Nebraska 7th Annual Commencement (College of Medicine), 1909 (Box 3)
  - University of Nebraska Botanical Seminar, 1895 (Box 3)
  - Uribe, Cesar, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Vaccarezza, Raul F., 1924 (Box 3)
  - Vanderstricht, O., 1919 (Box 3)
  - Vanhoffer, E., 1896, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Veglia, J., 1923 (Box 3)
  - Vejdorsky, F., 1905, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Vignal, L., 1925 (Box 3)
  - Vincent, George Edgar, 1919-1930 (Box 3)
  - Waite, F. C., 1909-1917 (Box 4)
  - Walcott, Charles Doolittle, 1921 (Box 4)
  - Walker, E. M., 1923 (Box 4)
  - Wardle, R. A., 1935 (Box 4)
  - Watase, S., 1893 (Box 4)
  - Weber, E., 1897-1903 (Box 4)
  - Weber, E. O., 1909 (Box 4)
  - Weismann, August, 1904 (Box 4)
  - Weldon, W. F. R., 1904 (Box 4)
  - Weltner, W., 1903 (Box 4)
  - Wenley, R. M., 1926 (Box 4)
  - Wesenberg-Lund, C., 1930-1931 (Box 4)
  - West, James, 1888 (Box 4)
  - Wetzel, Rud., 1930 (Box 4)
  - Wharton, Lawrence D., 1919 (Box 4)
  - Wheat, William H., 1941 (Box 4)
  - Whedon, Auther? D., 1924 (Box 4)
  - Wheeler, William Morton, 1892 (Box 4)
  - White, James M., 1918 (Box 4)
  - White, Stuart Edward, 1931 (Box 4)
  - Whitman, Charles Otis, 1890 (Box 4)
  - Wiedersherm, Robert, 1891-1921 (Box 4)
  - Wilber, Ray Lyman, 1914-1931 (Box 4)
  - Wilder, Harris Hawthorne, 1893-1896 (Box 4)
  - Willemoes-Luhm?, Rud. von, 1872 (Box 4)
  - Willey, A., 1904 (Box 4)
  - Williams, Steven R., n.d. (Box 4)
    Fragment
  - Wipperman, Lou, 1942 (Box 4)
  - Wise, Stephen Samuel, 1932 (Box 4)
  - Witenberg, G., 1926, 1932 (Box 4)
  - Wolcott, Robert H., 1914 (Box 4)
  - Wolffhugel, K., 1903, 1919 (Box 4)
  - Woltereck, Richard, 1931 (Box 4)
  - Wood, Casey Albert, 1913-1931 (Box 4)
  - Woodruff, Larande Loss, 1921 (Box 4)
  - Worcester, Dean Constant, 1893 (Box 4)
  - Wright, R. Ramsey, 1892-1894 (Box 4)
  - Wuhe, J. W., 1915, 1921 (Box 4)
  - Yajl, R., 1?25 (Box 4)
  - Yamagawa, K., 1895 (Box 4)
  - Yatsu, N., 1926 (Box 4)
  - Yokogawa, Sadamu, 1919, 1920 (Box 4)
  - Yoshida, S. O., 1914-1927 (Box 4)
  - Yerkes, Robert M., 1920 (Box 4)
  - Zacharias, Otto, 1898-1899 (Box 4)
  - Zapffe, Fred, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Zebusky, A., 1923 (Box 4)
  - Ziegler, H. E., 1903 (Box 4)
  - Zimmer, E., 1903 (Box 4)
  - Zograf, Nicholas de, 1898-1902 (Box 4)
  - Zschokke, F., 1898-1930 (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous Fragments, Unidentified, Other (Box 4)